

### CONTACT

985-870-6734 mikaelabeth96@yahoo.com

in mikaela-chiasson-knight

## **EDUCATION**

Nicholls State University
Bachelor of Arts
Mass Communications

Houma Christian School High School Diploma

# SKILLS

- Media relations
- Social media campaigns
- Web/graphic design
- Adobe products
- Creative & news writing
- PR campaign experience
- Managing colleagues
- Networking
- Re-brands
- Leadership
- Ambition
- Client Relationship Building

# MIKAELALhight

#### SUMMARY

Throughout my college education, I've learned how to use multiple communication theories, concepts and programs. I have worked well in the leadership positions I have held. I want to share my creativity while helping other's find their own. I know I would be an excellent addition to any team.

I have been working in the food-service industry for over 8 years. I am adamant on always showing up early and working as a team while maintaining a positive attitude. This experience has helped me have a full understanding of communication and appealing to a customer's desires.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### related experience

Garde Voi Ci Magazine | 08/2021-12/2021

Managing & Design Editor

Trash Free Waters Campaign | 01/2021 to 05/2021

Account Executive | BTENP | via Nicholls State

Junior Associate Internship | 06/2021 to 08/2021

Spears Group - New Orleans, LA

Freelance | 03/2020-present

Brand designs, event planning, concert flyers, social media

## service experience

SERVER/BARTENDER 12/2020 - current

Milano - Houma, LA

SERVER | 02/2020 to 12/2020

La Carreta Mexican Restaurant - Houma, LA

SERVER/BARTENDER | 09/2018 to 12/2019

Mill Creek Country Club - Mill Creek, WA

SERVER/TRAINER | 04/2016 to 09/2017

Texas Roadhouse - Houma, LA

## REFERENCES

Mike Slobojan (supervisor)	206-919-8242
Nicole Boudreaux (supervisor)	985-414-1934
Laure Kasovich (supervisor)	432-827-2689
Dave Angbrandt (supervisor)	985-647-5984